A Guide to the Papers of Walter Scott Copeland 1880-1954
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Correspondence
  - Jno. Garland Pollard to Elizabeth R. Copeland 1930 May 21 (Box 3)
  - Edmund Learny to Walter Scott Copeland 1930 Jun 6 (Box 3)
  - Louise to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1930 Jun 10 (Box 3)
  - Charles M. Graves to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1930 Oct 23 (Box 3)
  - Charles M. Graves to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1930 Oct 31 (Box 3)
  - Jno. Garland Pollard to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1930 Nov 25 (Box 3)
  - Howard E. Rondthaler to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1931 Feb 4 (Box 3)
  - Charles A. O'Connor to Walter Scott Copeland 1931 Feb 10 (Box 3)
  - A. Lawrence to Walter Scott Copeland 1931 Apr 16 (Box 3)
  - W. A. R. Goodwin to The Yorktown Sesquicentennial Association 1931 Aug 22 (Box 3)
  - J. A. C. Chandler to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1931 Dec 29 (Box 3)
  - Dick McGlohon to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1931 Dec 29 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Virginia C. Weddell to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1932 Jan 4 (Box 3)
  - Louis M. Howe to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1933 Jan 14 (Box 3)
  - Mrs. Julian Keith to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1933 Mar 23 (Box 3)
  - Richard F. Beirul to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1933 Aug 30 (Box 3)
  - Geo. C. Peery to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1934 Feb 16 (Box 3)
  - Geo. G. Ferguson, Jr. to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1936 Jan 18 (Box 3)
  - Geo. O. Ferguson, Jr. to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1937 Jan 13 (Box 3)
  - Stuart G. Gibboney to G. F. Ostargren 1937 Oct 29 (Box 3)
  - Charles M. Graves to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1938 Feb 17 (Box 3)
  - Carter Glass to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1940 Aug 8 (Box 3)
  - D. S. Freeman to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1941 Sep 4 (Box 3)
  - Geoffrey O'Hara to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1943 Apr 14 (Box 3)
  - Josephus Daniels to [Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland ?] 1943 (Box 3)
  - C. Vernon Spratley to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland 1950 Feb 16 (Box 3)
  - Walter Scott Copeland to Geo. O. Greene ___ Feb 19 (Box 3)
  - Fred W. Scott to Walter Scott Copeland ____ Jul 7 (Box 3)
  - Mary B. Dimmock to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland ____ Jul 28 (Box 3)
  - J. Laive Henn to Walter Scott Copeland ___ Sep 3 (Box 3)
  - Beverley D. Tucker to Walter Scott Copeland ___ Nov 17 (Box 3)
  - Jo Lane to Elizabeth Copeland ___ Dec 15 (Box 3)
  - W. R. Aylett to Walter Scott Copeland n.d. (Box 3)
  - Geoffrey O'Hara to Mrs. Walter Scott Copeland n.d. (Box 3)
  - Henry S. G. Tucker to Walter Scott Copeland n.d. (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1906 Apr 10- 1939 Apr 2, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation Papers 1924 Jan 8- 1939 Nov 28 (Box 3)
  - Letters, Telegrams, and Clippings of Condolence 1928 Jul-Aug (Box 3)
    re Death of Walter Scott Copeland
  - Letter fragments 1938, n.d. (Box 3)
- Business Memoranda and Papers
  - Memoranda and Business Papers 1890-1938, n.d. (Box 3)
    re Times-Herald
- Speeches, Addresses, and Testimonials
  - Speeches 1919-1928, n.d., 2 folders (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Papers and Printed Material
  - Miscellaneous Papers 1893-1939, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Memorabilia 1921-1931, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Photographs and Prints 1927, n.d. (Box 4)
    Two photographs of Walter Scott Copeland and Mrs. Warren G. Harding
  - Newspaper Clippings 1908-1954, n.d. (Box 4)
    chiefly re Walter Scott Copeland
  - Walter Scott Copeland's certificate of membership in the Associated Press 1909 Nov 4
  - Certificate appointing Walter Scott Copeland a Virginia delegate to the Centennial Celebration of the Monroe Doctrine held in Richmond, Virginia, December 2-4, 1923 1923 Nov 19
- Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook of Mary A. Christian 1880 Dec 25 (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook with a drawing of Walter Scott Copeland 1895-1920, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook of postcards ca. 1904 (Box 4)
    re Newport News, Va.
  - Scrapbook of clippings 1925 Jul 15 (Box 4)
    re National Editorial Association trip through Virginia
  - Item pulled from Scrapbook #1 1902 (Box 4)
  - Items pulled from Scrapbook #2 1891-1927, n.d. (Box 4)